Bob Bullock Comptroller of Public Accounts papers, Inclusive: 1970-1991, Bulk: 1975-1990
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Issues, 1971-1991; 2
  - Education, 1982-1991; 1
    - Education Correspondence (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - General, 1979-1991; 2
    - Ad Valorem Tax, 1979-1982 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Ad Valorem — Transfer to State Property Tax Board, 1979-1980 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Law Judges, 1982 November (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Admissions Tax — H.B. 504, 1979 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Agency Accomplishments, 1975-1977 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Agency Accomplishments, 1979-1981 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Agency Accomplishments — News Releases, 1976-1977; 1980; 1984; 1988 (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Agency Accomplishments — Report: “Money Management — Six Years Later”, 1982 (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - Agency Accomplishments — Speech Material, 1976-1977; 1980; 1982 (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - Agency Accomplishments — Statistical Data, 1975-1981 (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - Aircraft Pooling, 1980-1983 (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - Airplanes, 1982 (Box 189, Folder 12)
    - Appropriations Certified to Date, 1981 (Box 189, Folder 13)
    - Appropriations Bill — Texas (Clements), 1982-1983 (Box 189, Folder 14)
    - Appropriations Information, 1983 (Box 189, Folder 15)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1983 March (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1983 April (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1983 May (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1983 November (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1984 January (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1984 April (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1984 May (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1984 June (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1984 August (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1984 September (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1984 October (Box 190, Folder 11)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1984 November (Box 190, Folder 12)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1984 December (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1985 January (Box 190, Folder 14)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1985 February (Box 190, Folder 15)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1985 March (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1985 April (Box 190, Folder 17)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1985 May (Box 190, Folder 18)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1985 June (Box 190, Folder 19)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1985 July (Box 190, Folder 20)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1985 August (Box 190, Folder 21)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1985 September (Box 190, Folder 22)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1985 October (Box 190, Folder 23)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1985 November (Box 190, Folder 24)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1985 December (Box 190, Folder 25)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1986 January (Box 190, Folder 26)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1986 February (Box 190, Folder 27)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1986 March (Box 190, Folder 28)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1986 April (Box 190, Folder 29)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1986 May (Box 190, Folder 30)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1986 June (Box 190, Folder 31)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1986 July (Box 190, Folder 32)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1986 August (Box 190, Folder 33)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1986 September (Box 190, Folder 34)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1986 October (Box 190, Folder 35)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1986 November (Box 190, Folder 36)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1986 December (Box 190, Folder 37)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1987 January (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1987 February (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1987 March (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1987 April (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1987 May (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1987 June (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1987 July (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1987 August (Box 191, Folder 8)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1987 September (Box 191, Folder 9)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1987 October (Box 191, Folder 10)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1987 November (Box 191, Folder 11)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1987 December (Box 191, Folder 12)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1990 January (Box 191, Folder 13)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1990 February (Box 191, Folder 14)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1990 March (Box 191, Folder 15)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1990 April (Box 191, Folder 16)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1990 May (Box 191, Folder 17)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1990 June (Box 191, Folder 18)
    - Attorney General Opinions (1 of 2), 1990 July (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Attorney General Opinions (2 of 2), 1990 July (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1990 August (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1990 September (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1990 October (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1990 November (Box 192, Folder 6)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 1990 December (Box 192, Folder 7)
    - Audits — Tax (1 of 2), 1975-1982 (Box 192, Folder 8)
    - Audits — Tax (2 of 2), 1975-1982 (Box 192, Folder 9)
    - Audits — Tax — Gates, Ray, 1980 (Box 192, Folder 10)
    - Austin American Statesman, 1978-1982 (Box 192, Folder 11)
    - Austin Citizen (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 192, Folder 12)
    - Austin Citizen (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 192, Folder 13)
    - Austin Citizen Probe — Negative Press, 1976 (Box 192, Folder 14)
    - Austin Citizen Probe — Press Inquiries (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 192, Folder 15)
    - Austin Citizen Probe — Press Inquiries (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 192, Folder 16)
    - Austin Citizen (Last Edition), 1981 October 30 (Box 192, Folder 17)
    - Bailey, Blake, 1982 (Box 192, Folder 18)
    - Bankruptcy, 1982 (Box 192, Folder 19)
    - Banks — Holding Companies, 1982 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Bank — Tax (1 of 3), 1983 (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Bank — Tax (2 of 3), 1983 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Bank — Tax (3 of 3), 1983 (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1981 January — August (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1981 October (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1981 November (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1981 December (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1982 January (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1982 February (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Bingo: Correspondence (1 of 2), 1982 March (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - Bingo: Correspondence (2 of 2), 1982 March (Box 193, Folder 12)
    - Bingo: Correspondence (1 of 2), 1982 April (Box 193, Folder 13)
    - Bingo: Correspondence (2 of 2), 1982 April (Box 193, Folder 14)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1982 May (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1982 June-July (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1982 August-September (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1982 October-November (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1982 December (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1983 January (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1983 February (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1983 March-May (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1983 June 29 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1983 July (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - Bingo: Correspondence (1 of 2), 1983 August (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Bingo: Correspondence (2 of 2), 1983 August (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1983 September (Box 194, Folder 13)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1983 October (Box 194, Folder 14)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1983 November (Box 194, Folder 15)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1983 December (Box 194, Folder 16)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, 1984 February (Box 194, Folder 17)
    - Bingo: Correspondence, undated (Box 194, Folder 18)
    - Bingo: Correspondence: Bingo Regulations Division Notebook — Parts I — VI, 1982 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Bingo: Correspondence: Bingo Regulations Division Notebook — Parts VII — XII, 1982 (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Bingo: Phone Calls, 1981 November (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Bingo: Phone Calls, 1981 December (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Bingo: Phone Calls (1 of 3), 1982 January (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - Bingo: Phone Calls (2 of 3), 1982 January (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Bingo: Phone Calls (3 of 3), 1982 January (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - Bingo: Phone Calls, 1982 February (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - Bingo: Phone Calls, 1982 March (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - Bingo: Phone Calls, 1982 April (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - Bingo Investigation (1 of 4), 1988-1989 (Box 195, Folder 11)
    - Bingo Investigation (2 of 4), 1988-1989 (Box 195, Folder 12)
    - Bingo Investigation (3 of 4), 1988-1989 (Box 195, Folder 13)
    - Bingo Investigation (4 of 4), 1988-1989 (Box 195, Folder 14)
    - Biographical Information Requests, 1975-1978; 1982 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Blue Laws: 69th Legislature (1 of 7), 1982-1985 (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Blue Laws: 69th Legislature (2 of 7), 1982-1985 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Blue Laws: 69th Legislature (3 of 7), 1982-1985 (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Blue Laws: 69th Legislature (4 of 7), 1982-1985 (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Blue Laws: 69th Legislature (5 of 7), 1982-1985 (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Blue Laws: 69th Legislature (6 of 7), 1982-1985 (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Blue Laws: 69th Legislature (7 of 7), 1982-1985 (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Boards & Memberships — Bullock (1 of 2), 1976, 1981-1986 (Box 196, Folder 9)
    - Boards & Memberships — Bullock (2 of 2), 1976, 1981-1986 (Box 196, Folder 10)
    - Bonds (1 of 7), 1989-1990 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Bonds (2 of 7), 1989-1990 (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - Bonds (3 of 7), 1989-1990 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Bonds (4 of 7), 1989-1990 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Bonds (5 of 7), 1989-1990 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Bonds (6 of 7), 1989-1990 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Bonds (7 of 7), 1989-1990 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Bonds: Highway, 1983 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Bonds: State (1 of 2), 1983 (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Bonds: State (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Border Master Plan, 1990 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Briefing Information, 1982 September (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Brochure Revisions, 1983 (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Browder, Hon. Larry, 1981 (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Budget: Federal (For 1983), 1982 March (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Budget & Internal Accounting Division (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Budget & Internal Accounting Division (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Budget Requests — Agency, circa 1983 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Budget Requests, FY1981, 1979 March 12-1979 September 30, 1979 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Budget Requests, FY1981, 1979 March 5-1980 May 16 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Budget Requests, FY1983, 1981 May 21- 1982 May 19 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Budget Requests, FY1983, 1981 April 29-5 May (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Budget Requests, FY1983, 1980 June 9-1981 April 29 April 29-1980 June 9 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Business Climates: General Manufacturing, 1982 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Business Tax Division, 1982 (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Car Line Company, 1982 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Carter, Hon. President Jimmy, 1980 (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - Cartoons, 1981; 1983-1984; 1988 (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Cellular Phones, undated (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Census, 1990, 1989 July-1990 January (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Census, 1990 — Legislative Briefing (1 of 3), 1989 November 21 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Census, 1990 — Legislative Briefing (2 of 3), 1989 November 21 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Census, 1990 — Legislative Briefing (3 of 3), 1989 November 21 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Central Files — Complaints (1 of 4), 1989 January (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Central Files — Complaints (2 of 4), 1989 January (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Central Files — Complaints (3 of 4), 1989 January (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Central Files — Complaints (4 of 4), 1989 January (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Central Files — Complaints (1 of 2), 1989 February (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Central Files — Complaints (2 of 2), 1989 February (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Central Files — Complaints (1 of 3), 1989 March (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Central Files — Complaints (2 of 3), 1989 March (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Central Files — Complaints (3 of 3), 1989 March (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Central Files — Complaints (1 of 2), 1989 April (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Central Files — Complaints (2 of 2), 1989 April (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Central Files — Complaints (1 of 2), 1989 May (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Central Files — Complaints (2 of 2), 1989 May (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Central Files — Complaints (1 of 3), 1989 June (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Central Files — Complaints (2 of 3), 1989 June (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Central Files — Complaints (3 of 3), 1989 June (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Central Files — Complaints (1 of 2), 1989 July (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Central Files — Complaints (2 of 2), 1989 July (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Central Files — Complaints (1 of 2), 1989 August (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Central Files — Complaints (2 of 2), 1989 August (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Central Files — Complaints (1 of 2), 1989 September (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Central Files — Complaints (2 of 2), 1989 September (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Central Files — Complaints (1 of 2), 1989 October (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Central Files — Complaints (2 of 2), 1989 October (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Central Files — Complaints (1 of 3), 1989 November (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Central Files — Complaints (2 of 3), 1989 November (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Central Files — Complaints (3 of 3), 1989 November (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Central Files — Complaints (1 of 2), 1989 December (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Central Files — Complaints (2 of 2), 1989 December (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Checking Accounts, 1982 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Chief Clerk Notification Letters, 1983 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Cigarette Task Force, 1981 August 6-1982 January 4 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Cigarette Task Force, 1979 January 19 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Cigarette Task Force — Imbert, John Wayne, 1967 August 14-1977 January 21 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Cigarette Task Force — O’Connell, James John, 1976 April 20-1977 May 9 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Cigarette Tax — Correspondence — ANTI (1 of 3), 1989 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Cigarette Tax — Correspondence — ANTI (2 of 3), 1989 (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Cigarette Tax — Correspondence — ANTI (3 of 3), 1989 (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Cigarette Tax — Correspondence — PRO (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Cigarette Tax — Correspondence — PRO (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Cigarette Tax — Correspondence — Media (1 of 2), 1989 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Cigarette Tax — Correspondence — Media (2 of 2), 1989 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Cigarette Tax — Memos, 1989-1990 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Clements, Hon. Bill: General Statements, 1979 July-December (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Clements, Hon. Bill: General Statements, 1980 January (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Clements, Hon. Bill: General Statements, 1980 February (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Clements, Hon. Bill: General Statements, 1980 March (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Clements, Hon. Bill: General Statements, 1980 May (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Clements, Hon. Bill: General Statements, 1890 August-September (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Clements, Hon. Bill: General Statements, 1981 January (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Clements, Hon. Bill: General Statements, 1981 July (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Clements, Hon. Bill: General Statements, 1981 December (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Clements, Hon. Bill: General Statements, 1982 March (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - Clements, Hon. Bill: General Statements, 1982 April (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - Coalition For American Public Employees, 1979 (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - Communication Systems (1 of 2), 1982 March-1983 September (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - Communication Systems (2 of 2), 1982 March-1983 September (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - Community Involvement (1 of 5), 1983-1988 (Box 203, Folder 18)
    - Community Involvement (2 of 5), 1983-1988 (Box 203, Folder 19)
    - Community Involvement (3 of 5), 1983-1988 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Community Involvement (4 of 5), 1983-1988 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Community Involvement (5 of 5), 1983-1988 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Complaint Letters, 1980 November 20-1979 October 13 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Comptroller Certifications, 1975; 1977; 1979-1980 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Comptroller Certifications, 1981-1986 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Comptroller Certifications, 1987, undated (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 1 (1 of 5), 1978 October (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 1 (2 of 5), 1978 October (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 1 (3 of 5), 1978 October (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 1 (4 of 5), 1978 October (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 1 (5 of 5), 1978 October (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 1 (1 of 2), 1978 November-December (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 1 (2 of 2), 1978 November-December (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Investigations, Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 1, 1979 January-February (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 1, 1979 March (Box 204, Folder 16)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings (1 of 2), 1979 April (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings (2 of 2), 1979 April (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 1, 1979 May (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 1, 1979 June (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 1, 1979 July-December (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 2, 1980 February — April (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 2, 1980 May-July (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 2, 1980 August-December (Box 205, Folder 8)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock “Allegations” Clippings — 2, 1981 (Box 205, Folder 9)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Bullock — Files Defended, 1975 (Box 205, Folder 10)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Grand Jury Articles — Headline List, 1978 October-1980 July (Box 205, Folder 11)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Grand Jury Articles (Investigation), 1980 August-September (Box 205, Folder 12)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Grand Jury Report (Investigation) (1 of 2), 1979 March (Box 205, Folder 13)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Grand Jury Report (Investigation) (2 of 2), 1979 March (Box 205, Folder 14)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Grand Jury Report — Expungement Suit (1 of 3), 1979 (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Grand Jury Report — Expungement Suit (2 of 3), 1979 (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Comptroller’s Office Investigation: Grand Jury Report — Expungement Suit (3 of 3), 1979 (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Computer Availability, 1983 November (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Computer Availability, 1983 December (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Computer Availability, 1984 January (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Computer Availability, 1984 February (Box 206, Folder 7)
    - Computer Availability, 1984 March (Box 206, Folder 8)
    - Computer Availability, 1984 April (Box 206, Folder 9)
    - Computer Availability, 1984 May (Box 206, Folder 10)
    - Computer Availability, 1984 June (Box 206, Folder 11)
    - Computers — Correspondence (1 of 2), 1984-1987 (Box 206, Folder 12)
    - Computers — Correspondence (2 of 2), 1984-1987 (Box 206, Folder 13)
    - Confidentiality Statues, 1980 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1982 March-August (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Constitutional Amendments, 1983 October 25-1983 November 18 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Constitutional Amendments: Committee on Constitutional Amendments, 1981 December (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Constitutional Amendments: Proposed by the 65th Legislature, 1978 August (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Consultant Contracts: Miscellaneous, 1981 July-1982 May (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Convention Schedules — Comptroller Of Public Accounts Office, 1979 January 1-1981 July 24 (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Corporate Income Tax, 1978 January 27-1980 April 30 (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - County Officials: Anderson County: Visit, 1980 June (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - County Officials: Andrews County: Visit, 1979 January (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - County Officials: Angelina County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - County Officials: Aransas County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - County Officials: Atascosa County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - County Officials: Archer County: Visit, 1979 (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - County Officials: Armstrong County: Visit, 1979 (Box 207, Folder 15)
    - County Officials: Austin County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 207, Folder 16)
    - County Officials: Bailey County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 207, Folder 17)
    - County Officials: Bandera County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 207, Folder 18)
    - County Officials: Bastrop County: Visit, 1979 (Box 207, Folder 19)
    - County Officials: Baylor County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 207, Folder 20)
    - County Officials: Bee County: Visit, 1979 (Box 207, Folder 21)
    - County Officials: Bell County: Visit, 1979-1981 (Box 207, Folder 22)
    - County Officials: Bexar County: Visit, 1979 (Box 207, Folder 23)
    - County Officials: Blanco County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 207, Folder 24)
    - County Officials: Borden County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 207, Folder 25)
    - County Officials: Bosque County: Visit, 1979-1981 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - County Officials: Bowie County: Visit, 1979-1981 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - County Officials: Brazoria County: Visit, 1979 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - County Officials: Brazos County: Visit, 1979-1981 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - County Officials: Brewster County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - County Officials: Brisco County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - County Officials: Brooks County: Visit, 1980 (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - County Officials: Brown County: Visit, 1980 (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - County Officials: Burleson County: Visit, 1979-1981 (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - County Officials: Burnet County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - County Officials: Caldwell County: Visit, 1979 (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - County Officials: Calhoun County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 208, Folder 12)
    - County Officials: Cameron County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 208, Folder 13)
    - County Officials: Calahan County: Visit, 1980 (Box 208, Folder 14)
    - County Officials: Camp County: Visit, 1980-1981 (Box 208, Folder 15)
    - County Officials: Carson County: Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 208, Folder 16)